NIDHEY INDURKAR

Full Stack Developer

PERSONAL PROFILE:

Experienced Full Stack Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in PHP, Javascript, Angular, SQL, Ajax, and Github. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from Anjuman College of Engineering, Sadar.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- Markup Language : HTML5
- Style Sheet: CSS3, SASS
- Server Side Scripting: Php, NodeJs
- Bootstrap Framework
- C. C++
- Angular 8
- ReactJS
- MySQL, Firebase Database
- REST API
- JavaScript, Ajax, Jquery
- Node JS
- Python

ACHIEVEMENTS:

Participated and certified in 'Hackathon 2.0' program in innovation parv for starting the start-up project SWIRLLY

WORK EXPERIENCE:

PROCOHAT TECHNOLOGIES PVT. LTD,

'JUN 2020 - AUG 2021', FULL STACK DEVELOPER

ROBOVR,

'AUG 2020 - DEC 2020', WEB DEVELOPER

IDEAL VILLAGE.

'JAN 2020 - APR 2020', PHP DEVELOPER

TAKE IT IDEAS,

'MAY 2019 - JUNE 2019', TECH. LEAD

PROJECTS:

DailyTroops: E-commerce Web Application for Groceries, and various services like plumbing, carpentry, car wash, etc.

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, PHP

Link: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.daily.dailytroops&hl=en

Team Size: 2

Oily Handshake: E Garage Services for Regular Bike and Car Service, Manual Repair and Washing, Emergency Road Side Assistant.

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, PHP

Link : http://dailyvry.in/OilyHandShake/

Team Size: 2

MintLime: A portal where developers can sell their Html website templates, photographers can sell photographs, and much more. The customers can buy the templates and edit them according to their business needs.

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, PHP

Link: https://mintlime.in/digital/template_shop.php

Team Size: 1

Fineffi: Lead a group of 5 developers and had developed a mobile application that automates the working of solar pannels. The application gives the realtime time generation of solar energy on daily, monthly and yearly basis.

Link: https://fineffi.net/

Team Size: 5

CONTACT DETAILS:

Address: 1563/17 Vaishali Nagar Binaki

Layout, Nagpur 440017 Home: 8975620020

Cell:7020793286, 9096810774 Email: nidhey60@gmail.com

Website: https://nidhey27.github.io/Nycto_Nid-

site.github.io

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nidhey-

indurkar-a9638b179/

Github Link: https://github.com/nidhey27/

Face Recognition using JavaScript: The system detects the face, age and mood of a person.

Link: https://github.com/nidhey27/face-detection-usingJS

Team Size: 1

Video Calling Application: Basic Video Calling Web Application using NodeJS, Express, and Socket.io While using Google meet, Zoom, and Other meeting platforms, I wondered how these applications allow us to connect using audio and video. So tried to clone such a video calling app.

Node Packages used: Express, Socket.io, uuid, and Pressjs

Link: https://github.com/nidhey27/videoCallingApp

Team Size: 1

Virtual Mouse: Built a virtual mouse that can control your personal computer using your fingertips. You can perform left-click, right-click and double-tap to perform various operations on your PC without touching IT

Technologies used: Python, OpenCV lib

Team Size: 3

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:

RASHTRASANT TUKADOJI MAHARAJ NAGPUR UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer science & engineering,

Anjuman College of Engineering and Technology, Nagpur

Academic Year: 2017 - 2021 Aggregate: CGPA 8.77/10

MAHARASHTRA STATE BOARD OF SECONDARY AND HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION.

Sindhi Hindi Junior College, Panchpawali, Nagpur

Academic Year:2016-2017 Aggregate: Aggregate: 67.69 %

CENTRAL BOARD OF SECONDARY EDUCATION (CHENNAI)

Bhavanas Lloyds Vidya Niketan, Wardha

Academic Year:2014-2015 Aggregate: Aggregate: 69.20%

CO-CURRICULAR AND EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES:

- Active participant in cultural activities of the college
- Represent the college at the university level in Volley Ball

STRENGTHS:

- Quick learner and Strong willingness to learn new things.
- Ability to cope with failures and learn from mistakes.
- Co-operative attitude.
- Adaptable to changes.
- Self-motivated.

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Date of Birth: 27 Mar 1999Mother Tongue: Marathi

• Languages Known: English, Hindi, and Marathi

• Area of Interest: Reading Novels, Music and Sports, Bike Riding,

Traveling.

DECLARATION:

If given a chance to be a part of this organization. I assure to work with full dedication and to the best of my abilities.

PLACE:

DATE: